Max Brokman

Flat 11 Denning Point, E1 6DH 07841 386 184 max@mangosix.co.uk mangosix.co.uk/max

Profile

I am a driven and self-motivated developer with both front-end and back-end experience. I have successfully converted a teenage interest in PHP into commercial development experience through hard work and self-directed learning.

I'm friendly, confident, passionate about web applications and famous for being tall!

Key Skills & Technologies

Object-Oriented PHP, Laravel, Codelgniter, WordPress, phpunit. MySQL. HTML, CSS (LESS), RWD. AngularJs, jQuery. Experience with REST and SOAP APIs including extensive experience working with Soundcloud and Google DFP / AdX. Git. AWS EC2, S3, SQS. Beantstalkd, Elasticsearch.

Employment

Aug 2014 - Web Developer (business systems), Vice Media Inc.

As part of a team of four I work on maintaining, refactoring and expanding an ERP application which supports sales, display advertising planning & management, and accounting & reporting.

I have particular responsibility for finance tools, which I have recently substantially refactored to improve reliability, accuracy, speed and test coverage.

2013 - 2014 Web Developer, Civil Music / Hyponik.

http://civilmusic.com, http://advance.civilmusic.com

I developed two websites for an independent record label. The first is a customer facing website with audio delivered through Soundcloud and direct sales through Topspin.

The second site offers advance copies of new releases for press and industry, supported by email-based marketing tools. Downloads are watermarked through a system which makes extensive use of distributed work queues and AWS autoscaling services.

2007 - 2013 Theatre Technician and Stage Manager, Various

Theatre is an extremely high-pressure industry and I gained valuable experience in time management, adapting to changing requirements and working in and leading small teams.

Education

2011 - 2014 BA Hons. Anthropology & Development Studies, SOAS, University of London (2:i)

2009 - 2011 Physics, University of Oxford

I left Oxford at the end of my second year for personal reasons.

2002 - 2009 The Latymer School, Edmonton

A levels: Maths (A), Physics (A), Politics (A)

Interests

I'm a keen (injured) road cyclist with CC London (http://cc-london.com/) and a house music DJ.